after eating countless pints of the
first three recipes I decided it was
time to diversify the portfolio these
pints will be half the calories of Halo
Top Taste even better than Halo top and
will only take three minutes to make
make sure you stay till the end because
I will tell you some bonus tips to take
these creams to the to the next level
let's get into it if you know anything
about me you know I love Oreos my Oreo
McFlurry was uploaded nearly one year
ago to the day so it is a perfect time
to make it cereal counterpart get a pint
on a scale and add 160 grams of one
percent high protein milk like Fairlife
280 grams unsweetened almond milk and
2.1 grams vanilla extract yes 2.1 grams
I highly suggest you have a point scale
for these recipes or your recipes might
not turn out exactly how you'd like
anyways put a small bowl on a scale and
weigh out 50 grams of swerve 1 gram salt
1 gram xanthan gum and 8 grams of black
cocoa powder this is exactly what Oreo
uses in their cookies giving this ice
cream a much more authentic taste and
this brand is by far the best in terms
of real Oreo flavor also once you have
it you can make things such as my Oreo
cookie dough and Oreo flurry as well
using a spoon fork or whisk blend all of
the dry ingredients together so they
have an easier time dissolving into the
wet ingredients then using a hand
blender slowly start pouring in your dry
ingredients once all dry ingredients are
mixed in blend for an additional 90
seconds this will ensure an even flavor
throughout when finished put a lid on it
and throw it into your freezer after 24
hours grab your Frozen pint and run it
under hot water for 40 seconds once
finished dry off the Pint and load it up
hit the ice cream button and let it do
its thing while that's going let's weigh
out our cereal of course the cereal of
choice is Oreos 10 grams when the ice
cream is finished immediately load it
back up and hit the respin button do a
happy dance until that finishes and
unload your pint using a knife make a
hole about the width of said knife then
load that cereal in there I personally
like to leave five to six pieces to top
my ice cream with so put those to the
side load it back up and hit that mixing
button tap your pint with the extras and
it's time time to eat as the Oreo flavor
flows through your taste buds let's move
on to our main man Fred and his Pebbles
of chocolate get your Pine on the scale
and add 160 grams one percent milk and
280 grams almond milk then in a separate
Bowl add 50 grams swerve or pure cane 1
gram salt 1 gram xanthan gum and 8 grams
of cocoa powder I highly recommend this
King Arthur cocoa because the quality is
outstanding and I will be using it in my
protein brownie recipe coming out very
soon as well but at the bare minimum you
should be using a Dutch processed cocoa
blend to get that deep chocolate flavor
mix all the dry ingredients thoroughly
and then slowly mix them into the wet
ingredients once finished continue
mixing for 90 seconds quick tip use
masking tape to label your pints if you
have an addiction like me and have a
bunch of flavors being made at the same
time throw it in the freezer and wait 24
hours there will be no waiting for me
since I already have one sitting in the
freezer which I highly Rec recommend you
buy extra pints so you don't have to
wait 24 hours ever again either when
ready grab your pint rinse the outside
of it for 40 seconds and dry it off get
it loaded up and hit that ice cream
button immediately followed by the
respin button while it's spinning let's
grab our Cocoa Pebbles or coco rages in
my case and weigh out 10 grams into a
bowl knife out a nice Circle in the
middle and load it up with the goodies
like the last recipe I like to leave a
couple grams off to the side to top with
for a greater mouth feel and texture
load it back up and use the mixing
setting and lastly but optionally but
highly recommended load up a waffle cone
with two or three scoops and enjoy if
you're enjoying these recipes please
give this video a big fat thumbs up and
if you want to make sure you see all my
recipes the day they come out make sure
you hit that notification Bell as well I
don't think it's right to talk about
chocolate without talking about peanut
butter grab a pint throw it on the scale
and add 160g grams fat-free milk 280
grams almond milk and 4.2 grams vanilla
extract in a separate Bowl add 45 grams
swerve 1.5 grams salt 1 grams and then
gum and 8 grams of powdered peanut
butter per use mix the dry ingredients
together and slowly mix them into the
wet ingredients if a little hits the rim
that's okay nothing a good old finger
slide can't fix keep the blender going
for an additional 90 seconds and get
that thing in the freezer the next day
rinse it pop that top off and load it up
push that ice cream button and
immediately after we spin it grab your
Reese's Puffs and weigh out 8 grams
create a tunnel in the middle of the
Pint stuff it with that peanut buttery
goodness and load it back up hit that
mixing button after the mix and cycle
you have a smooth creamy Reese's Puffs
ice cream pint that you can enjoy for
less calories than two peanut butter
cups I promised bonus tips and through
the testing process I have found small
tweaks can make for an enormous Flavor
Boost first with the Oreo cream mini
marshmallows are our best friend take 10
grams of them and when loading the
middle stack Oreos and marshmallows on
top of each other until you reach the
top if you run out of room just add more
and push them down so you can have more
mix-ins throughout each bite of ice
cream then top with the remaining
marshmallows and Oreos to make for the
complete dessert while only adding 33
calories to your pint if you want to add
an even deeper chocolate flavor in your
Cocoa Pebbles cream add one to two drops
of coffee extract before you blend and
you're all set any more than this will
make your ice cream taste like coffee
but a couple drops will just enhance
that chocolate flavor every time it hits
your tongue I don't know about you but
in my opinion peanut butter ice cream
can never have enough peanut butter
flavor during the mix and setting stage
Take 5 grams of peanut butter put it in
a small bowl and microwave it for 30
seconds you can either tap directly into
the pints or scoop some Mount into a
bowl or if you're feeling spicy a Waffle
Bowl and top onto your cream This truly
takes this recipe to the next level for
just 30 additional calories Oreos peanut
butter or chocolate I would say make one
of each and try them all while having
these three recipes is great there are
three more that even have less calories
than these three which you can see here
six recipes down many more to come until
next time deuces